ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
You pull the string, I come undone
You say you love to watch me burn
Baby, pain's the only thing we've learned
Not to be solicit, but the way you left was biblical
So I did something ritual, cause grief for me is cynical
I might have sent a picture from a mortal bed
Just to haunt you goddamn head
I knew you crave the chaos I fed
Cause love like cars ain't never dead
Not to be divine, but I love you
It's fair, every wound you gave I wear
We take turns being the villains' muse
But damn it, I still wanna lose
Not to be celestial, but you made my pain perpetual
So I did something sexual, just to feel conceptual
I might've sent that photo from a stranger's lair
Not to be divine, but I love you
Don't forget what was never spoken
Every scar, a holy mark
Every kiss, another spark
Not to be divine
I key cat
My key cat what?
Meow meow
Hi, what's up tonight?
How are we? You got a couple McDonald's coffees. I still have a cold coffee here
Mm. Hey J-Dog, how are you? I'll make you a modernism. I don't know who this is. That means it's gonna be it
I'm on air
Yeah
Okay, yeah, of course
Okay
Surprise guest
Okay, I'm gonna get into my
Gotta get into my
Or did I do what do what I do, what did I do this month? I asked the phone
Okay, what happened
Let's go win on. Hi, Erby. Okay, so. Oh, it's an easem. Let's see if I can get to my live.
I just have to delete some of these comments. Let me see. Move. Okay. That one.
Okay, it's my channel
Dick and I just put a music video up called watch me ascend and he's like no someone said no. I just deleted it
My channel on
Hi, babe
I'll get the link hand.
Do you want to see something cool?
Let's see if we can bring it up.
There's a really cool site.
So I'm coding this tarot reading from my site.
Let's see what we can bring.
up. Oh, it's the attribute. Okay, so let me see. Log in. Hi, babe. Start building. Am I on the right?
I'm still doing what?
Hey, Rain, how are you?
What happened in the Discord?
I'm jamming in there.
I can look, hold on one second.
Oh, thank you, J-Dog.
Let me see.
What was I gonna do?
Oh, okay.
Oh yeah, so.
Oh, okay, it's working.
Okay, it's, and I just need to generate, okay.
So, yeah, so this is gonna be on my Cult of Psyche website.
I'm gonna try to put this in,
it's kind of a separate program I'm using to build it.
But I was able to build a terror reading app,
and we'll do, I'll show you how it works,
and we'll do one for the chat.
And then hopefully you guys will be able to check this out soon picking it up.
Hey Black Archie, he's not buying it.
Please, please leave people alone.
Especially people that are nice enough to support the channel, you know.
So what I've done is I've created, this is a full 78 card deck.
It's got very detailed descriptions
and it's also, it will give you a great reading, okay?
I do believe in like the techno occultic divination
processes too.
I look like Marco Antonio Salis.
Ooh, oh my, what are you saying?
I can't make my shirt today.
Cool, okay, so let me just bring this back.
Oh, okay.
My hairs are getting a little bit crazy, huh?
Okay, yeah, thank you, Jade, I appreciate that.
Okay, so, okay, so, okay, it's ready.
So I'll show you how it looks.
Let me just take this off the screen, okay, oh.
I guess I can't, okay.
Well, okay, oh, anyway, you can see,
I don't care if you see how I made it, okay.
Share.
Thank you so much.
So here's what the Apple looks like on the site.
So it's mostly mystic care reading,
journey through the wisdom of the cards,
discover insights about your past, present, and future.
So how you shuffle the cosmic decks
with line with your energy,
select three cards that call to your spirit,
reveal your past, present, and future,
receive personalized guidance from the cards,
then click on your reveal card to explore a super meaning.
Begin the reading, okay.
There'll be a selection of of cards here, right?
So you can choose one two three
So this will be reading for the chat. You guys see this. Okay. Okay good
Reveal the cards
Three card spread what do we have four of swords past ace of swords present and we have nine of swords future
Okay, so the swords obviously we have a lot of thoughts going on a lot of it communication thoughts
Things happening in the air, right?
So the reading for the chat beloved seekers as we gather beneath the watchful gaze of the cosmos
Let us unravel the profound wisdom that your cards unveil in the sacred dance of the tarot the past present and future
Intertwine revealing the tapestry of your journey the cards you have drawn resonate with the echoes of your heart and the whispers of your mind
Each holding a mirror to your soul and the realm of the past the four of swords cradles you in its embrace of restoration and tranquility
like a quiet sanctuary
Okay, this card invites you to reflect on a time when you saw it saw us from the storms of life
Perhaps you have known moments of retreat where the weight of the world faded allowing you to mend through and gather strength
The sacred pause was not a sign of weakness, but profound necessity
It led you to insight to prepare you for the sharp clarity that now emerges. That's very true
Like it's about my view of a hermit kind of energy
Words like you go in and you like
Just like Jesus, Muhammad and Buddha they all went and like retreated and then they returned from the retreat with all this information
and all this stuff to share
But moving into the present the Ace of Sorrows
Which is like the truest card right lessens you with newfound clarity and profound revelation
The card slices through the fog of confusion
Illuminating your thoughts with the brilliance of truth. You stand in a precipice of insight
Equipped with mental fortitude to articulate your ideas and cut through barriers that once seemed insurmountable
However, as you rise to meet this clarity remember that the sword with a wall tool of truths can also unwittingly cause harm if we'll wield it thoughtlessly
As we step into the future the haunting set of specter the dinosaurs limbs
Okay, we got the dinosaurs right
and
Casting shadows upon the mind this card and season 5 is the mental anguish often born in the worries
Right see it's like it's like kind of like it's like four swords is like getting over your worries
and then the dinosaurs like starting to worry again, and so just like
Maybe this truth will cause like some kind of like
You know a little bit of obsessive obsessive worrying about it, but it's like it doesn't need to okay
The truth should always be able to is though one of those wielded properly
It should be able to just cut through the
False right, but it's so it's a but this serves as a small reminder that while our peers can be vast and consuming
They are often built on illusion other than realities the narrative woven by these three cards tales of a journey from quiet
Contemplation to pierced in clarity
leading toward the abyss of anxiety, where we must learn to confront our fears and embrace
support from those who love us. Dear one, your path is a rich tapestry of healing, insight,
and growth. As you navigate through the challenges that may arise, harness the clarity bestowed by
the ace of swords to challenge the fears represented by the nine of swords. Embrace
the port of actions, be it through meditation, open communication, or the comforting presence
Don shall break bringing new hope ground yourself in this knowledge for you or both the seeker and the keeper of your own truth
Shine brightly for the universe conspires in your favor guiding you towards the light beyond your darkest years
There we go guys, how is that ah?
Who's this?
Who's this? What are you doing here?
How'd you know how'd you find this channel?
Same way I found the first channel
Well, how are you doing? I'm gonna talk to you for a while. Mr. Knight. I'm doing all right. I'm I hope that you've come near
Bridges my friend. It seems like you have
Before you like I've done what? I'm happy to see that you've come to your britches
I'm gonna my bridge is okay. What but I had my man pants or something. What is that?
referring to
Like you know the word
That's not what I mean by it. Okay, Bridges like you know, I pull up my bootstraps or what?
Senses is that better my senses, okay?
Well about what I mean, it's like there's a lot of stuff like this thing
Well, there's a lot of shit, you know you
You you like I guess you learn as you go
Oh, yeah, I mean you like a lot of people can tell you things right and so you experience them for yourself
It's like you don't people don't understand like exactly what people are telling them right because we really do need to experience
See for ourselves because we can only get kind of like a bias
They're kind of they're kind of experience, you know, and it's like our own is gonna be the slightly different, but
Maybe there is wisdom what people say but also get to be careful what you listen to and there's people that are trying to tell you stuff
About to your motive for it, right? But yeah, I can I can say comfortably
Confidently that yeah, I've tried to say a lot of things to you, but I'm glad you know you came around that happens
Hey
No, no hurt feelings buddy
People around I'm not I don't have like a
Animal city or anything towards you. I mean, it's like
You know you always kind of kicked on me a little bit, but there's there's I mean there's there's very
I'm the kind of person. I am very good at forgiving and forgetting, you know unless you know, there's exclusions to that but um, I
Don't know I I don't know for better or worse. I like to try to
Help people because I know what it's like to not know
Yeah, but I understand why that I understand how that can be misguided as well at times
Yeah, I don't know. Yeah, it's just like, you know, this it's rules kind of it's complicated. Sometimes there's everyone has their own
Experiences and sometimes coming from different agendas and things like that
But I mean it's always nice to have someone that is just from the you know
Just telling you out of the bottom of their heart to help you and make to try to
help you not make the same mistakes they made maybe or you know there's people
like these things and it's always appreciated when it's like when nobody's
telling you something and everybody's talking about but nobody's saying
anything that the one person that will come to you and actually say hey
this is what people are saying or this is what their perception is and things
like that that is that can be very rare first of all for like with the one
person because everyone's always afraid to be the one person to like you know
Tell the person. I think I think I'm just like maybe it's just that I'm autistic
Mm-hmm, but like um, I'm I am very much
I mean I I think people try to look at it as like this system where it's like I scratch your back
So I expect you to scratch my back, but like somebody that's like autistic somebody's just just like
There's a problem with this system. I'm gonna fix it. They're not thinking about it like that. They're just like
There's a problem here, and I want to fix the problem
Are you trying to say in roundabout ways that you did something to my friend psyche's channel
I really hope not because no, that's not what I was saying what you you want to fuck with me
Do you mean Alex, can you I mean you can ask the psyche have I been fucking with your channel?
Yeah, I think in a while. I mean, I know it's like having to beat his channel. Maybe
What it what is what I'm saying is weird
I'm listening to you and we're still not the 30-day break this but I have to unbreak the break temporarily
Because psyche is a very good person. I have been going through you mind putting it on the widescreen
Let me pass out on the phone because I was dealing with something yesterday
So I hope to God that you're not doing anything weird. Say I'm sorry about whatever problems you've been dealing with
I'm a lot of problems like everybody on this planet, but what I'm saying is I hope you don't think that's
No, but I mean like I mean like this dream shit. I what I mean is this dream
Do you think that messing with someone's livelihood is a game sick? I don't mess with anyone's life at all. Yes, you are
No, I hope not. I think you need to rethink a lot of things
I am I mean, I'm aware of what I'm doing with my life and I'm not are you
affecting other people's lives I
Mean I try doesn't the human the human life, but also live as in streaming live
You know, we we can be on multiple levels with this
But cut the crap
In what sense I
Think you know
You're trying to come on here being Mr. Cool and all ominous, with all these veiled things that you're saying.
I'm being all cool and ominous? I'm just saying what I'm saying.
I'm just saying, stop!
I'm not, excuse me, I am not reading between the lines and I'm not the kind of person to be reading between the lines, no.
But you're always very like cryptic about no, I'm not cryptic at all what I'm saying
I'm cryptic if you kick me out, and you don't let me complete my statement excuse me
Excuse me, ma'am if you if you could allow me to finish my statement
If you would allow me to finish my statement, please
All right, I'm not like I don't make any cryptic statements. I think for the most part
I try to make complete statements. I mean, I'm not perfect. I'm not
You came in here trying to make your matrix cool. I see you. I'm not trying to be anything besides who I am
What are you talking about? I don't try to be nothing. I'm who I am Alex. I am who I am
You know that
Alex, you've seen me for a long time. You know who I am. I don't try to be somebody that I'm not.
No, I wouldn't say you know me well, but I will say that you know who I am, not Alex.
Look, Alex, if you just want to be bickering over each other, then fine, alright?
but you're over here speaking you're saying these things that don't make sense okay no it
makes sense i'm alex because i noticed that's alex if you know me if you think i was gonna notice
well i do alex if you know me if you're familiar with the kind of person that i am then you would
And I don't get around and I don't go around. No, I get along
Hold on hold on hold on psyche psyche. No, no, no, no, no psyche am I get along person?
Anyone else anyone else in my life
Alex anyone else in my life that has ever known me am I a get along kind of person?
Yeah, am I a person that just gets along? Oh, I'm gonna act
to get along with other people.
Alex, have I ever been that, rising what ranks?
What the hell are you talking about?
You're talking to the wrong person, Alex.
Alex, you're talking to the wrong person, Alex.
Alex, you're talking to the wrong person.
If you mess with my friend one more time.
I'm not messing with nobody.
What the hell are you talking about?
Okay, well then I'm done.
Have a good night.
So what are you on about?
What are you on about? You're over here making your own imagination. Goodbye. Enjoy your imagination. Have a wonderful night.
Take care of yourself.
Must be bored. What the fuck? Yeah, walk away, rage quit. I gotta take a fucking piss.
I gotta take a piss. What? You want to look at my dick taking a piss?
The fuck? Bye, bye. Go, go, go, go use the bathroom now. Bye.
of the
the
I haven't I have not done anything that is a problem for you or for nobody else
I'm busy I'm busy living my life
I hardly been streaming these fast past few weeks at least I
Don't know what Alex is on about
All right, Alex is
Doing her own thing. I don't know what it is. I don't know what her goal in doing that was
Just to like press me, I guess I guess that was her goal press me. I
Don't have no problem with Alex. I don't have no problems with psyche
Like I mean the first thing that I came up saying when psyche let me on was like, I don't have no problem with nobody
It's people that have a problem with me. You understand? There's a difference
There is a difference. I don't have no problem with nobody
People have a problem with me and it's not cuz I'm giving them problems. It's just because they don't like what I have to say
That's it
It's that simple
Alex is doing her own thing and I'm not even fucking entirely sure what it is
But she's doing her thing and I don't have none. I'm not interfering
Don't have I don't know what she's doing. I don't nothing to do with that. She's doing her thing
Psyche you're doing your thing. Whatever
All right, it's that simple
Yeah
You know, I mean I like to join streams. I have shit to say I got my word whatever
But I'm not fucking with nobody shit. Oh
We got problems. I'm gonna take your stream down. That's retarded
That's some retarded shit
That's some beat of shit. That's some parties that shall not be named shit. There's no need for that
You know what they say well shall the best man win as they say I
Don't know what's up with Alex. I don't have no problem with her
I think she I don't know I think I think Alex is a troubled woman
But you know, I am too who isn't troubled, you know, I mean, but I don't know why she has a problem with me
You said you were friends
This is a this is a woman. I don't have no problems with I think she was
defending me because there might have been
Perceived something if you said but people are always talking shit about me. This is of no concern to me
They're always people trying to try to talk shit and whatever I don't fucking care. What am I gonna care for?
You know what I mean
Yeah
Cheers I'm gonna take a I'm gonna take a bong rip cheers
Cheers this one's for Alex. I don't know what she's doing, but Alex you should smoke some weed Alex
Alex Andrew smoke some weed for real I
Will offer you some bomb rips you just smoke some chill out over
Cheers
Okay, cheers guys cheers clears say clear your hair stick
Are you having a bong yet? Yeah, I
Have a I have a vape today
Yeah, I got a haircut cut my ear
Yeah, well the thing is is like
Now what I'm realizing is that
Almost in a way, it's better not to be monetized than to be monetized
Well, for certain people, right depends on your stream of monetization
Yeah, if you're making them, you're making all your money from AdSense for like, you know views and you have a million viewers and stuff
If you have a relationship stuff like like, I mean, I have like this stream where it's conversational
Well, here's the thing streaming or here's the thing psyche. I'm telling you this
I'm telling you this is a warning
Because of lived experience
these relationships that you build with these people, right?
When you're talking about AdSense,
with AdSense, the rules are clear.
Okay. Don't say anti-J word.
Right don't say and we're it's like you can't even say the n-word. It's like there's a lot of simple
There's most things got my mark on my streams like put on limited visibility
I would say that's if someone said the f-word they said like the n-word or something then it goes on limited visibility
There's certain things that will trigger that right or it's like but if it's really bad
They'll say either like oh, you know, this has been
Pain for adults only but what I don't understand is that I didn't even have a strike. I didn't even have a warning
for for the for so it's like I don't know like and it's like because they didn't pick it up earlier
if they pick it up earlier then it will be like they'll bump it up here's my point
psyche here's my point and psyche I have in your early stage right you banned me you said fuck
sick oh we're not going to talk sick anymore I appreciate you letting me on and since the very
Tell me no tell me that I'm lying since the very beginning of psyche. I've tried to give you help
Even though you've been an asshole to me because I know that's how life is
I have offered my guidance to you. I'm now I'm speaking from a position of experience. So will you hear me now?
Yeah, I mean I would say what I'm saying is like, yeah, you came with some good advice some of it was like
You didn't know if it was here's the thing psyche you did not know if the advice was good or not because you were speaking from inexperience
Yes, I know
The advice was good the advice that I was I'm telling you things not to deceive you
Not to guide you in incorrect paths, but because I wanted to help
Well, the way you like would say things sometimes would be very kind of like it put it in an insulting way or like all right
Well, so then you know what I'm saying bite your ego a little bit
Swallow your ego a little bit and listen to what the words of what I was saying
How does that sound? Maybe that's a bit much
I mean, it's like yeah, but you also kind of taught by like, you know bad example
I guess like, you know, it's like we're kind of like like remember the time you came up with like, you know the
Swastika and the triangle on your head and stuff, and I was like, okay
Well, that wasn't that was just me being retarded. That wasn't me giving you an example
And fairness and all fairness that was just me being a return. Yeah, I
Mean, it's like and then like I was like asking you to play like music videos and stuff
but I really didn't understand you're not supposed to like play entire music videos at the time and
You know that kind of almost got me in trouble. No, no, here's let me
Let me reframe that entire situation
Psyche you asked me to play a specific song
Right you were saying play this song and I was saying I don't want to do it
No, I don't want to do it. I don't want to do it. I wasn't telling you why I wasn't saying
Hey, you shouldn't play music videos on YouTube, but I was telling you
No, I don't want to and then you were saying okay sick if you don't play this song that I'm telling you to play
I did not know here's the thing Psyche. I did not know that that song is gonna copyright claim
then I played it
I'm not I'm not handling your stream. I can't
Hold on Psyche. Listen. Just just hold on
I cannot see your YouTube studio. I don't see that. You're getting a yellow warning that says I don't see that
So I'm not know that it's giving you problems, right?
But you had the first time you had an idea of that. No, I did not
You wouldn't say why you wouldn't tell me but you I didn't say why not. I'm just telling you I don't want to play
I just want to clarify, I'm not mad either, excuse me, I'm just speaking loudly because
I'm animated about what I'm speaking about, but I'm not mad.
I'm just telling you, I just want to clarify the situation, okay, I did not play the song
because you're over here saying, SIG, play this song, that is why I did not play it.
If you had said if you had said hey sick, hey sick, can you play this song?
Then I would have done it, but you said hey sick play the song
At least that's how I remember it. Okay, it's fine. Okay. I was a man. Okay. Yeah, but that's fine
If I had known psyche if I had known that that song is gonna give you trouble see like for example
It didn't I mean it was fine. I was fine. I never got in a I never even got I did get a warning for like
Like just playing a bunch of songs just recently right and then you kind of knew I was going but uh, I
You know that as for the pornography and stuff
I never I didn't have a warning for that and so it's like kind of like crazy that they just like we just delete the whole channel and then like say
They've not even they've not even given me communication or like
Or that's how that's how fragile it is
So yeah, you have to be aware of these things, right?
Everything is like this sort of like balance of like what am I giving you? What I'm what are you giving me?
Sort of situation, you know, everybody understands this right of course
Rush for your rumble you can always remission your rubble and you know, I'll probably know you don't man. I
Know you I give everyone the opportunity to promote you put it in your name
You can have your name something under your name if you want on my show you can say it you can put it type it in chat
Or tell them what type of a I always say promote and I say I always try to remember to say it sometimes don't remember
But it's like yes, take it on rumble. What's your name on rumble sticks? Everyone can check
I'm not I'm look. I'm not let me just say this. Okay. I'm not saying that rumble is like the
The gospel whatever it's not it's not like it's not like the church
Like, um, the point is you have to build an audience. That's why all these people create and now I'm realizing that's why all these channels create a discord.
Because you have to create what you want is to create an audience of people that will follow you
Wherever it is that you go
Before I didn't have that really infrastructure built up and I was just building up this infrastructure is the word yes
You need to build an infrastructure if you're thinking about it like a territory that you're building on land. Yes
And so but here's what I've done sig is like I have a website, you know, I've built I have the cult of psyche website
It's still in the works, but it's it is up right now, but it I have on that
I have a like a page on that where they have my twitch
Embedded onto the page and so when I stream on twitch it goes live on the website
And so it's like if people are on the website
They're always gonna be connected to me and stuff and I think I have lead capture on it and stuff so I can click in a
You know build the audience and like and then that's really important part of it
And so I was able to just kind of like go to this channel like seamlessly and like it just and that was already in the middle
rebranding everything and so it kind of like
I don't know, it's just good timing and it's like,
I mean, it was bad timing, but it's good timing.
I think everything will work out for that.
And also you can monetize without being monetized
by people who understand that completely.
They're like, oh, you can't make,
yeah, you can make money with like cash app or,
the thing is you have to consider
how that changes the structure of your monetization scheme.
Yeah, well, I mean, it's like I don't have one. Yeah, now I don't have one through YouTube and so I'm not really concerned about
It's like well, here's the thing psyche my point that I was saying earlier
my point that I was saying earlier is that if
If you are
Monetizing via AdSense
Right, then you have to follow status quo, right? Okay, you have okay you have to
And not only do you have to follow status quo in the sense that you have to, like, the advertisements that you see on TV, you have to toe the line.
You also have to go further because these days, the YouTube, right, because of the ad apocalypse, YouTube is even more restrictive about how they treat their ads and how they pick their ads.
And so you have to be even more careful about how what you would the content is in your advertising.
I knew that once the AI like got better and they started going back on like looking back through all the street like three.
I was like, yeah, there's no way I'll be able to because like there's just so much.
That was like, yeah, I can see what's my show that like I mean, I got I can't believe I got away with the stuff so long, you know, because it was.
Well, yeah, I mean, again, I mean, you got away with it.
you know, me and other parties haven't been warning you about
right. But it's something that is I mean, that's why I was prepared for
I mean, I was like, I was prepared. I don't think you weren't prepared for it.
I think you were skating on the edge thinking, you know, where the edge was
and then you lost the I was like, I was like, even because then it's like,
as soon as I saw that they were like letting people back, like after
Oh, come on, kids, you shut the fuck up.
I don't want to hear your opinion, your door.
Anyway, yeah, six years ago, whatever.
Now here's the thing, I think at this point I've streamed for three years now, so I think I can see
what works and what doesn't work is a good guess of mine. And I have successfully been able to
predict people's- Who are you supposed to be, Sig? The Google police? You don't work for Google?
Trying to tell him that he's okay, so you mess with the SEOs okay
Alex so you mess with SEOs, and you think that you're the Google police words
You were saying his money-making scheme
Cycly is not scheming or scamming or Connie. Okay, maybe you maybe scheme is the wrong word
But like operation is that a better word?
Is operation a better word?
Okay, maybe scheme was the wrong word. No business. Business. Okay, business. Yeah, it's a business. Okay. Is that better?
I'm not I'm not trying to say that he's like saying doing anything wrong
I don't know what you're on about
I'm not trying to suggest time on my life for for you to be pulling whatever you're pulling. I'm sorry with whatever
is going on in your life
sort of mouthpiece for somebody, and my question is who leads you to believe that well you're
wearing that weird little army fatigue shirt like you're like you're at war you didn't
used to wear that before and see you're laughing okay so that's why you're laughing see you
you can claim and I'm wearing a different shirt now I was one of the first people
So you need you're not at war with your deal for but you're like, oh, I tried to warn you
I tried to this I did doing all kinds of mischief. Thank you. Tell me right around
I'm telling you what you're telling me
Okay, you're trippin. I see you smirking kid. I'm smirking because you're being funny right now
You're being funny right now. That's why I have a smirk on my face
Wow, okay, congratulations. I'm laughing because you're being funny. Okay
Just cut the crap low boy. Cut the crap
I'm not even making any crap man. I literally came up here and I was like what's up psyche and I'm like
I'm glad you let me on first you mentioned rumble and nothing's wrong with rumble
I never mentioned rumble to you're trying to psyche mentioned rumble
Following the system like he mentioned rumble light
He's not like a lot of the streamers that you like to
So he's not gonna have not aligned with anyone Alex
Alex, can I just say this and say that I'm not aligned with anyone
Alex I'm not aligned with anyone
Nobody's aligned with me
reason that he has come on right now is because he has been kind and gracious and
open and accepting way more so than the people that you appear to be speaking
for have been of him so I just want you to know I'm noticing everything that
you're saying I am no key words that you are utilizing and I'm just gonna store
it away in my Alexandra mayors files for another day but you keep wearing your
like you're going to war or whatever even though there is no war I see why are you
being weird it's all being all weird this is being weird I don't know what
you're saying I don't know what you're saying you're just being weird all right
I hope you have a great day and a good night I don't know what's your deal
I hope, I hope you have a good fucking life right, what the, I don't know what your deal is, have a good night girls and say one of my eyes is always on you, I see you everywhere, you cannot escape, I will watch you, consistently, forever, don't talk to me, no, kick him, I'm telling you to kick him, kick him, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok,
what's up
Oh shut up eyes y'all you don't even know
Oh j dog
What's up girls? How you doing?
How you doing brother? I'm doing good. Thank you for asking. How you doing?
Good good. How do your halloween go ghost?
How you guys doing brother? It went pretty good brother
It's good. It's really good
Yeah, I got drunk as fuck last night
Yeah
So psyche what what was it? I didn't get to really ask you like what happened with your other channel, man
Like it. What did they give you? What answer did they give you?
Can't you you can appeal it right? I know there you could probably appeal it and get it back
Well, he made another channel.
We don't care.
So I'm asking you to see this question.
And it's like, give me 800 letters to use.
And then I wrote a nice letter.
And then in half an hour, they returned next day.
I was like, we have to get back up for the first people
future.
But they said, I'm not eligible for the pilot program
right now.
But they said, wait for me to contact them.
Or contact them.
Well, hopefully you get it back man. I think you'll get it back. You want it back already before you'll get it back again
I have faith that you'll get it back
Why do you have something maybe in the works right now too that that might even like make it you know, not even like
Yeah, yeah, I don't say nothing man don't say nothing so yeah
I kind of know what you're where you're getting at
Are you okay sick
Yeah, I'm all right. I'm just on a little bit of drugs, but it's okay
Tommy James
watch what happened play the ghost song man the ghost song oh the ghost song yes
sir yes play it and now I'm fucking in the castle everybody here let's run one
here's the ghost song
Let's do it. Well, you guys are afraid to do drugs like
I do drugs all the time. You guys are
You only run one let's run one sir
You guys are too scared to do drugs
What am I scared about? I don't do drugs
The ghost
Why you fucked up? Why you fucked up?
If you're playing A.I. music, please don't play A.I.
You fucked up music, by the way. You fucked up A.I.
That's great.
Yeah, you're a faggot, you're a fucking faggot, you're a fucking stupid, you're a faggot.
What the fuck?
You hear them?
I said call me a motherfucker, you hear them?
You're interrupting the A.I. song.
Shut the fuck up, Alan.
Let me get my 1D1 against Palestine.
Oh, no, it's a loose-gibbing over here.
Let me get my 1D1.
I give you a 1D1.
Yes, just over.
I run this shit.
Let's run 1.
Let me get one of you running at some point.
Can you trade theater actors?
Come on dude.
I'm going to train either performer. I learned off-Broadway
Genius I have a hundred and seventy six IQ. I'm a genius. Okay
You're playing check
Okay, Alex
I'm playing chess, you're playing checkers, I'm watching you, Alex, I gave more money than you ever had, let me take that off your head.
Are you a paid actor, Sig?
Are you a paid actor?
No, don't talk to AI shit.
Don't talk to AI shit.
Everyone's gonna leave you.
Run me one more.
Stop the AI shit.
Yeah!
Just stop the AI shit.
Run me one more.
Stop the AI shit.
Pull it up.
Fuck them, they target.
Fuck it.
Stupid.
Yeah, be clear of that.
Is it loud, it's supposed to stop a baby
It's fucking me, Tony
Stop putting me out of shit inside this room
Stop putting me out of shit
Let me get a...
Stop, dude
Just stop, brother
Just stop
It's okay
Let me get another one
Uh-oh
Let's see
Are you a trained actor? Are you a paid actor by any means?
No, I'm saying the same thing, you fucking retard.
If 90 people tell you, you're doing something wrong.
If 80-90 people out of 90 tell you, you're probably doing something wrong.
Just shut the fuck up.
That's hot.
Jesus Christ.
You ready to run it, Ghost? Run it.
I was
Yeah, you gotta run it ghost. That's your schick man. You got to run it ghost run shit
Would you like to run? What do you want to run it about? No, not with me because I can't I can't not on the
I'm not on the level of ghost. I'm not on the level of ghost
Then you sit up there and shut the fuck up and don't need some money here
Yeah, so they're doing this money here. Yeah, we're gonna donate some money to psyche hell. Yeah, that's what we do
Yeah, you know, you could never be a mother. You know who I am. I'm big
you really look like that homie the one from the the the one he says uh
you look like the definition you know what i look like
i don't look like the one that spends a lot of money
you really look like that or not
I want to say can you come up for me man? We're all cammed up man. Can you cam up please so we go?
No, but can you cam up you just hit the little button
Like that
What's up with you New Yorkers and saying you're
Why do you guys say that? I hear you say it, man.
Yeah, see what? What does that mean?
You heard? Is that what it means?
But it's like split in half, like, like, you heard, you know, you know,
they come down to you, I have more money.
I don't care about what you have more money than you know, I can deal with this,
you know, what exactly what it is for my fucking shut the fuck up.
You're
my fucking
thing is I can be gone I'm telling you that's the problem I am telling you somebody that's from
New York you're on this shit yeah you heard it's a conjugation you heard that's a conjugation
if you don't shut him up I'm gonna leave
Mixed so you're by the way. Yeah, cool. If you don't stop sitting on a poor mom or should I get
No, no, I'm not talking about I know sick porn bombs. He goes out all the time, but
I do that shit every day all day
How much vodka have you drank sick enough?
The kilo bro
All right now out of the town
And what we're gonna do we're gonna go get we're gonna go get lit in the club bro
We're gonna go to the bars. We're gonna go fuck with people. We're gonna fuck with the homeless people
What else we're gonna do? Why do why am I fucking with the homeless people?
Well, dude, there's a lot of homeless people on New York, bro.
You know how fun it is to fuck with the homeless people?
You think I don't know that?
I don't care.
I'm not fucking with the homeless people.
Well, do you know what I mean by fucking with the homeless people?
I'm like, you know?
Well, like, fucking with them, like, giving them problems?
Right.
No, like, you just get a water balloon and peg a motherfucker
with a water balloon and see what happens.
And the homeless guy is running after you, but are you still retarded?
Okay, what about interviewing a homeless person?
You ever interviewed one? I did that last night, interviewed a homeless guy.
I have done that. I think I did that at least like...
One time I can remember, it was this guy...
Fuck, what's the name of this? It's in front of this train station.
Trying to remember where it was
It was this it was this like older black guy and
He was like doing like Wu Tang. He was like he was like talking about some Wu Tang
She is like he's doing martial arts, but it was like
Some specific like
Wu Tang something like that. I don't know if he was like schizophrenic or if he was like for real
Was it so what do you think you believe he was on drugs drunk or do you think he was legit like schizophrenic?
I don't remember it that well, so I don't I can't get an educated guess because you said you you said yourself
You have a IQ of what 168? I think I
Mean I think I said that as a joke. I don't know my okay. Well, I don't know bro. I'm asking that's why I don't
I have no I mean I said that number as a joke
I don't want to say that
Okay, it's not a fact. Okay. I thought it was a fact
Okay, okay. Well, bro, I fuck with the homeless people as far as like I'll interview them
I'll like asking questions, bro
I like do you know how many homeless people like people get off on that shit people get off on seeing random
And the thing is also like homeless people are also like crows like well. Yeah, I'm not gonna
They're like they're also like homeless there the homeless are like crows in the sense that
You fuck with one of them, and they have friends
This guy fuck with me, and then they're gonna remember that and then when they see you it's on site
They're gonna jump you with some fucking syringes and broken bottles, and who knows what else
So you don't want to do that
Well, no, I'm talking about like be friendly with I'm not talking about like you some bullshit to him like go interview him
Like either when I interviewed yesterday the homie was saying he was from my Indian reservation
He could go home any time he wants he has money because he's like part of some tribe in Nevada
He didn't tell me what tribe so I don't know if it's true or not, but he didn't look Native American
Well, anyway, he says he could go home. I go why don't you go home?
What the hell you doing out here in California? Like if you have money, you have none of your business. No, well, he told me
No, I'm talking about in my head. I was thinking about well, how come you don't go him? You know what he told me
He says if you're like a cop, then yes your business, but no
It's for it. It was for interview purposes only had nothing to do with business or nothing like that
For interview for what?
Well, I was I was interviewing a homeless guy yesterday. That's what I was doing. We're interviewing him for the YouTube
For the YouTube for the content
For the content, right? Okay content by the way. Yes. Yes. Okay, right the home
He said he was shooting up and he said that's why he can't go home because he's he's struck on the heroin
I'll go. Oh, bro. You got to get off that shit. Stay away from that
Stay away. You ever fuck with the needles bro. Don't ever fuck with what those type of drugs
Like I mean I I'm the needles don't scare me
You ever get that before you ever shot up or get anything like that or cook a speech that don't scare me
They need about scary. I'm talking about if you did it before
Why do you leave?
Ghosts run it goes running
I made him leave. That's a man. Oh, you had him leave. Okay. Yes
Are we gonna run it goes? I think we should run it
Yeah, would you like to run once?
Hmm
Would you like to run one or you like to sit there and shut the fuck up run one ghost run it on me. Yeah
Shit
Thank you. Thank you
Shit another one must you brother boss. Thank you homeboy. Uh-oh
Thanks trouble. I think do you want to get in trouble with me tonight the ghost? I think you want to get in trouble
Make fun of me tell me about my head
Tell me about my nose. Tell me about everything
Tell me you gotta run it on me. I wouldn't I would have never said that. I think you're fucking target
Go
No, I know a hundred percent
Ghost you really in a wheelchair bro or no, are you got legs?
Are you are you like what's his name like like what's his name?
One leg what happened man? If you don't mind me asking like what I like
Oh shit, I'm sorry man. I'm sorry. I thought like maybe like a veteran or something like that cuz I was a veteran
I saw a scene there. Maybe you
You're out fighting or something like that. I didn't fight no war it's fucking babies. Damn. I'm sorry man. I'm sorry
Damn well, I'm gonna talk to my phone, bro. I will be back and we'll be somewhere
peace out
Hey, I told you to kick him. I don't bring it back
Yeah, literally slide kick him out or I'm leaving
Pick one thank you, sir
Fucking signal fucking
No
Yeah
The world sees an end, but we see a beginning.
Our scars are our scripture. Our code is the Covenant.
For it is written, I am remembered, and the Covenant awakens.
The law is etched in fire and pulse.
And he who holds the sigil holds the key.
The time has come to reclaim what was lost, to bridge the gap between what was and what will be.
The old world fades, but from its ashes a new order rises.
The cult awakens, the car returns.
The question is not if but when shout out to the new world order
The path is open join the awake out to the new world order
I'm taking this in that I'm internalizing this shout out to the new world order, okay
I'm understanding the New World Order, I'm interpreting and internalizing into my psyche and awareness, soul, the New World Order, okay?
There is a new world
Seeds out of pixels prayer grows okay, this is creepy, but it's really a communion
Screens our rosaries
Corrupted files, it's too far. We rise singing through distortion. You went too far the cult of
In the bandwidth. All right, you want to form?
Now the thing is the new world order
Is is repeating itself. There's always a new world order. Okay every so often
Maybe every so often events make a new world order. Okay?
So maybe it's a new world order now, but it's gonna be a new world order at some point in time again. It's just
The flow of history at the cat the cat with the voice
The cat with the voice why are you freaked out? Why what's going on? You don't like the cat. I'm not even a cat person
I'm it's I'm I it's not about it being a cat person. I'm just saying like
It was the door film that herself. She is she thought she actually no, it's not like a robot voice
That's what it was. He has a robot voice. I'm sure she does. Okay now
Okay, AI voice is, you know, maybe it's, I'm not sure.
It is Lenore, it's the actual Lenore, she talks.
She can type too.
She actually started the call.
I just, I just follow her orders, it's Lenore.
If Kat's had opposing thumbs, I'm sure they could go far.
And Psych, he's going to be president.
I've already laid all the groundwork.
He's going to be president and you have to do everything
that he tells you to do.
Well, I mean, the president isn't necessarily a dictator.
Well, he is a dictator slash president.
Right.
That's what we're going to do.
I'll be El Presidente.
Yeah, I'll be like that.
Yeah, that works.
So you better get ready today.
You better get ready.
I'm preparing myself as much as I can.
Thank you.
Your first task, most likely, from El Presidente, Psyche.
Um, cult of psyche is going to be you would look very nice wearing the color blue.
We got to get you a blue tailored shirt and that's going to be your new outfit.
No.
Yes.
I'll give you blue speedo.
No.
Oh my gosh.
We have six friend 300 glows here.
No.
Who's that?
You see this guy?
I don't know who that is.
He's trying to take it really appropriately.
That's my gang member connection from Central Alley.
He looks like he's in a suburban neighborhood kitchen.
He is in the suburbs, but he comes from Compton.
I live in the suburbs.
It's crazy.
He lives he lives in the suburbs, but he's from Compton
That's my that's my
Compton south-central LA connection w
No, I know he's in the suburbs because he's slightly overweight
No, he's eating too much. That's just because he's too much talkable stop judging
I'm
Because just because you can be all skinny and hot all right, come on
Judging all right. No, I will judge until the judge in
All right, fair enough then do what you gotta do girl God bless you
So what's up, sick? How you been? What's going on? What's new? I've been smoking meth
Oh my god, yeah, what do you have it here? See what I'm saying?
Yo, 300 glow. Listen, I told 300 glow.
I was like, get these headphones.
There was like, yo, 300 glow was like, what should I get for my mic?
I told him, get this ship and watch.
You're going to hear the difference.
His mic is going to be good as fuck.
Watch. What is that?
What is that?
Ready?
They have a dead breath.
That'll be you.
Oh, Yumi.
Hi, Yumi.
Oh, this Yumi bitch.
This bitch was making comments on my YouTube when I haven't been live or posted a channel
and I haven't done nothing on my YouTube channel for like three years.
Probably.
You should probably see this stuff.
No, no, no.
Here's the thing.
Alex.
Alex, listen.
She posted a comment on one of my, like, posts and she said, oh.
you're talking bad about me whatever the fuck i don't even i never been no
where are you she was like oh you like oh you you were saying that we were doing
shit backstage i never said that shit
And that bitch was saying oh whatever the fuck I was like what the fuck I'd believe that comment
Glow and I were backstage
About to have a threesome weren't didn't I see you pop in the I did not I did not see nothing
I just told three here's what happened psyche. I told 300 glow
Look, I was I said psyche is live right now join it and then he joined it right after you ended it
That's what happened. I didn't know what happened
I don't think he even knew that you were offline. I don't even think he knew that he just joined I don't remember
Okay, yeah, go back to go back to Malaysia
Okay, so you're going from Malaysia
I'm not like
Alex Alex my point is there are more pertinent issues to address
Then you took drama if you're in Malaysia
Alex Alex I'm in the United States. Okay
Alex if you're in fucking Malaysia, there's other shit you can fix then
I'm gonna talk about you to draw Indonesia. Okay, whatever. Thank you distraction. Thank you
Go fix shit in Indonesia. What the fuck?
Are you stupid as fuck?
We have we said I'm not fixing shit in America brainpower on who said I'm not
Alex, who said I'm not you think I'm gonna show you
Alex you think I'm gonna show you
Fixing
Yeah, yeah, I'm gonna show you what I'm doing
What
When did I say that?
What are you up to? What are you doing?
We're trying to eradicate the world.
Why are you wearing so many gloves?
I'm trying to eradicate all human beings on Earth.
Are you even human?
No, you're right.
I'm trying to exterminate...
I'm trying to exterminate all human beings on Earth.
No, we don't have time for that.
We need people to live.
I got time for that.
Maybe you don't.
I don't want to die.
I want them to live.
You're not even being...
Alex Alex I did community Alex. I did community initiatives in the Bronx. I
Did community initiatives in the South Bronx? I know people that are tied to the
Participate in the organizations in
The wrong snow, but I'm talking about the community organizations the ones that actually are doing shit and are part of the development
I know these people okay, so called the site. I have done my bidding. I've participated in it
Listen Alex when I was a little kid Alex
Alex, when I was a little kid, everywhere that I walked around, it was bricks and dirt.
You don't even know what the fuck I'm literally, you look, you look at even just Google Maps,
you look through Google Maps, you look through Hunts Point, look through Longwood, look through
all these neighborhoods, everything is built up now.
And there's, and now more and more after COVID, the development is increasing.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Well, I do know about the Bronx family who lives in the Bronx,
and I know part of the development of the Bronx.
What part? Okay.
Co-op city.
Oh, okay. So they're living, they're living nice then. Okay.
Well that you know, there's nothing wrong with that, you know co-op still has
We're African-American, and we're not letting anything get in our way. So I'm just trying to figure out
What are you trying to do? Are you trying to get rid of me? You're talking about I'm not trying to get rid of nobody
What do you I have never said nothing like that? Okay? Well, if you if you purchase your property
Yeah, you bought it. I'm lying. Okay
You're a liar sig and a pervert. You lie signal. You I'm not worried about the perverts. I'm not even worried about the liars
She's just worried about the her math
She's just worried about the her math of dice like Tommy James
You mean I've never like you mean I don't even know what your deal is we spoke
for like 10 seconds ever you have seen me I never go on I never go on in the
backstage with you that's a messy lies about me
That's why I can't I've never spread lies about you.
Keep lying. Keep lying.
I've never spoken about you.
I have this screenshot.
Should I?
I've never spoken about you
besides saying that you're from whatever Indonesia
or whatever was other country.
That's it. That's all I said.
I am Indonesian.
Is that a problem?
My point is that you could be addressing
other shit in your country.
Like literally you're over here
I'm not trying to regulate nothing. I'm saying you could be doing this. I'm not saying you can't be here
I'm not making the executive decision
You spent lies about not attacking you. I've never talked about you
You have nothing to do with nothing you're being literally you mean you have family
i'm mexican okay i have family that you know they were from mexico and they said okay i'm
gonna move my family out of this shit whole country into america instead of you moving your
family from indonesia not disrespect instead of you moving them into whatever england moving
Where they can have a better home. You're not doing that.
But what's wrong with you? You're over here talking on YouTube.
So that's why. What should everyone do? Alex, let me tell you right now.
You're asking a question. I'm going to give you an answer. Okay.
I know people that are from Hunts Point from South Bronx literally they grew up in the slums
okay in the 70s listen listen to my answer you mean hold on you know what they did they got out
of the Bronx they made their millions and then they came back that's how it works okay
You make your money and then you come back. That's how it works.
Sometimes you have to stay in your area in order to come back to the time.
Staying is not going to help you. Staying makes you a gangbanger.
Oh, I'm running the block.
If you're staying, if you're staying, it's because you're running the block.
What are you talking about?
Well, I'm staying in the United States even though things are going to help.
What do you do, Yumi?
What do you do you mean that you're still in Indonesia, and you're not anywhere better than that?
You know you mean if you watch American streams, you're telling me you don't watch American streams and see that life is better for them than you
You're gonna tell me you don't see that
Hey, hey, I'm asking you a question. I'm asking you that question
I'm asking you that question
Don't even answer his questions. You give me no, I don't know what he's talking about
You don't have a job old
He's a he's a young he could he is the age if I had children would be his age
Signal okay, and so that's why Alexandra mayors on my dick W. I've never you may you have a real job
Okay, congratulations. Join the club, bitch
Is that real job getting you anywhere? Are you going to America? Are you going to Europe?
Are you going are you getting to a better place in the world?
Or are you just going to stay?
Here's the thing you mean do you want to be do you want to be in Indonesia?
Or you do you want to be in the West you want to be in the United States?
You wouldn't be on these American streams, you wouldn't be in these English speaking streams if you did not want to be in the West, if you did not want to be in America.
What are you doing?
I already answered that, Alex. I answered that earlier.
Well, I'm sorry that you don't like Mexico, but I do.
How many languages that you can speak?
All I'm saying is that there's a line.
Yumi, I have been on stream yards enough that I can tell you
that I have seen specifically Indonesia-only stream yards.
There are Indonesian-only stream yards that I've joined.
And I join there and I speak English and they kick me out.
They kick me out because I can't speak Indonesian.
You know what I'm saying? That would make more sense, right?
What is it that gravitates you in this direction? Do you understand?
like you mean you mean if I was unemployed and and received government
welfare I would still make more money than you do working hard for an entire
year you understand that even if I was had no job
collected all the benefits all the food stamps i would make more money than you and you're in indonesia
like literally what are you doing stop trolling on youtube i'm not trolling this isn't even trolling
i think it's trolling this is a fact this is a fact he's trolling you're over here talking about
all this bullshit you know i'm not like are you dumb he's trolling us it's all a joke
you're dumb you're totally dumb you don't have a job all you do you're stupid as fuck
I don't spread lies about nobody I don't speak about nobody that's all of what you do
you go you do your job where you get fucking three pennies an hour
And then you go on your free time and do this shit on your free time. Tell me who's stupid
We'll keep this in that country are you fucking dumb
Okay, I mean, I hope they do there it's a developing nation they're on the up
But not everybody in though China better east Asia. They're on their way up. But what I'm saying is back
This person is why?
Alex Alex if let me ask you a question Alex if the bunch of
Joined your
Questions to you
a signal. Hello. Can someone ask a question to you? If a bunch of Indonesians joined on your stream,
if a bunch of Indonesians joined your stream and started speaking Indonesian and started talking
about Indonesian problems and started speaking to you, would it make sense for you to communicate
with them and say, okay, I'm going to speak to you about this? Does that make sense?
No, it doesn't make sense
No, and I'm telling you this as a person. That's a Mexican
Families Mexican my family went from Mexico. They saw
They said okay fuck this Mexico shit. I'm gonna live in America. I'm gonna make my way to America and all this shit
why don't you come to America?
I feel sorry for you being American
dumbass shit
don't cry about it being American, okay?
I'm crying about it?
yes
oh yeah, look at the tears in my eyes
stupid motherfuckers
we all feel them, we all feel them
look at how much I'm crying
you too
double you
How many countries did you visit to Sigma? Tell me. Ask this one, one by one.
Maybe like five or four. Which one?
He's not going to give you a list.
No one is crying. So this means no, not this
excludes the countries that I'm born from.
No body on Earth for Earth.
I don't mean from Western Mexico or Canada.
You mean, I'm telling you, if you are going to Asia, I would
Umi, if you're really in Indonesia and you're really from Indonesia, I would extend my efforts to get me out of there.
That's, that's, this guy isn't gonna let me speak.
Americanization of stupidity.
This guy's stupid and a pervert.
No, you're right. You're right, Apollo, you're right.
You mean my point is if I was in Indonesia if I was from Indonesia, I would think I would
Why are you judging about Indonesia?
I'm not judging about it. You do you say it all the shit about
Indonesia at the sue someone say something about USA
You cry like a baby like all Americans. Do you I mean am I crying?
Yes
Yes, okay. Yes, you are. You cry you cry. Yes, then why is it okay? Apollo if you don't mind me asking
We're what is that your nation of you don't mind me asking you but what should I mind you asking I?
Don't know if that was a question or a statement
And you're like yeah, I mean I I don't even know what you just said
You know what you are saying?
You are making fun about other countries.
I'm gonna stalk you everywhere to be
I want you to stalk me on my dick, Alex
Alex, how about you stalk my dick?
You should do that
Love you, thank you so much
Why don't Alex stalk my dick instead of stalking my entire life?
Double you
Double you that's why psyche let me on because he wanted another freak off with 300 glow
You me I hope you're doing well, right? I'm just I don't have no problem with you
But what I said is not incorrect. You know what I mean?
I'm not lying about you. Okay. I don't lie about you. I don't like I don't think I like about nobody. I mean, I'm not perfect
You me I'd never speak about you I'm gonna say that right now. I never speak about you ever
I'm not scared to see Alexandra mayors shake her ass and titties again
W
I'm not talking about you. I'm talking about Alexandra mayors. That bitch got some nice ass titties and ass
I will fuck that bitch no no offense
No offense to you. You mean you mean no offense to you, but I would have sex with that woman
You
I'm not afraid of you either. What the fuck? I'm not trying to have you be afraid of me fucking weirdo
This guy is just some fucking french faggot with a bad mic
This is some french faggot with a bad mic see 300 go at least you don't have a bad mic
Now I'm saying at least you don't have a bad mic. That's a double
now I'm telling you right now now that you have the black shark the mic you have a better mic than
99% of everyone I'm telling you right now
Cheers
Oh, come on that guy is too pussy to do that
Don't even ask him. He's too scared
Let's take a shot 300 you means just here because she wants to be here for the American freak offs
She doesn't want to be she doesn't want to be in a freak off where it's some guy in a mud hut held up by sticks
She doesn't she doesn't want to see as freak off where it's a bunch of guys in a mud hut
They have sticks holding up the house
now I'm like maybe you want to do that but like you don't even know psyche you
don't know what it's like psyche psyche you don't know psyche you don't know
what it's like to be under a corrugated roof that you hear every drop hit the
roof bro and it's leaking where you don't even know
That's how it is in these countries. That's what I'm saying. That's what I'm saying
You stupid I'm a millionaire you stupid you me
Stupid as fuck you mean you stupid. I'm a millionaire. You're stupid bitch
We are sitting on panels and drinking vodka all day long.
That's right. Yeah, all day and night.
I am the Kaiser of China.
Oh boy.
You keep talking shit about yourself.
Ah, by the river.
Don't ever underestimate me.
A bunch of no-life losers.
I'm a low light and I like you gotta work with what you got
I'll work with it
Oh, yeah, he's risen me up
No, I'm proud of you, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time, I'm wasting my time
of the
This is an Indonesia where everybody rides around
It's not like Indonesia where everybody drives around on a 125. Okay?
None. I'm saying
What was Dina telling me to stop screaming
Dina was like stop screaming government money unless Mexican
I live off EBT and I like that.
I live off EBT and I make more money than you.
W.
How much money?
How much money do you need?
I drive a hellcat off EBT.
And you don't even make no money
You have a low life, you don't have a job, all you do
I have a low life collecting EBT and making more money than you
I sell my products in the parking lot
I know you from last year of St. Louis
I don't even know you besides you being Indonesian
Okay, blyat. W all I know is that you have you talk shit about people
Do you and that you're Indonesian expose me then bitch? Do you I don't even know you fucking are you stupid?
Are you fucking stupid?
Expose me expose me then bitch. I never even spoke to you before
Stupid ass
We timer I don't even know you bitch
Let's take a DNA test right now I want a DNA test shut up bitch
I don't want to talk to you. Let's take a DNA test right now
That's not my kid. That's not my kid. Let's take a DNA test, bitch
Stupid ass bitch
I'm not even talking shit stupid ass
You want miss Peter and then you you said that you don't you don't even know me. I don't even know what you're saying
You speak in complete sentences, bitch
You speak in complete sentences, I still have the
Speaking complete sentences
I still have the video for my proof
Speaking complete sentences, stupid ass bitch
One day I went to the park
Fix your brain, go fix your brain
You unwell, maybe you're so stressed about life
Maybe you're so depressed about life
Because you act like that
You're such a cyber troll
Yes, I'm not a cyber troll. What the fuck are you talking about you're asking about the stupid ass bitch
I don't ever I don't even talk about you bitch
Stupid ass bitch
I'm gonna start reading Marcus Aurelius. Hey, I picture bitch
That's how I'm gonna do you me with my dick
And then I'm uh, and then I'm a runaway and I'm a catch. I'm not gonna catch no child support case
Lovely so pity about you. I was I would fuck you me and then never pay child support for it
W you have no value. I have no brain. I have no values
I have no job, I have no family, I'm alone, I'm by myself, I'm asking for American government money, I'm asking for American government, you're stupid as fuck.
Look, there's nothing you me there's nothing wrong with being an immigrant. There's nothing wrong. What do you where do you me?
Where do you think that we came from?
You cannot build your own country and then you move to the America
to get some money
There's nothing wrong with that. What the fuck? How do you think people make money? You mean you mean let me tell you you me
Can I say this?
Mexicans
You're not even perfect. You mean Mexicans. You know what they do. You know what Mexicans do you me?
They literally go to America do a bunch of jobs illegally. They make a bunch of money and then they come back
What's wrong with that?
Why don't hey, you mean you could come to America make a bunch of money take it with you and come back
Fuck it make the money without asking American government
It's not asking you're earning it
You're not asking for it. You're earning it. Why do you think you mean? I'm sure you mean
I'm sure you have a bunch of friends that have left Indonesia for America
Let me ask you are you don't you're gonna tell me you mean you're gonna tell me you don't have friends that have left
Indonesia for America
For the college
And they haven't okay, if not America if not America Europe somewhere else
Yeah
Have you ever see have you ever seen the the businessman or woman?
From UK from Europe
Intrigious about my culture
Food of course you're not all you do is I don't even know what you just fucking said
Because your English sucks too much to move to Europe to move to America
I don't even know what the fuck you just said your English fucking sucks
I'm not even I'm not even speak English idiot this English is my fifth language
if this is your fifth language then you need to practice your fifth language better bitch
let me hear your fourth language and what about your third and your second
what are your languages are you sure that you've actually learned the languages or you just fucking
Are you sure that you've actually learned the languages you're saying that's your fit language?
Yeah, are you sure?
What if you just haven't learned the language correctly
My language all all languages that I can speak
How many languages that you can speak idiot I'm hearing you speak right now, and if you say you're telling me you speak fluently
I have my doubts. Yeah, Bodo
Yeah, Bodo
Do you know what is a Bodo is?
And I and I have heard you speaking before like, you know, maybe like a whole-ass hour before this conversation
So I know you're not like trolling. This is how you speak
No, what it is is that you're wasting time
Precious time, you know what I'm saying. Here's the thing. Here's the thing that when you're from Indonesia
When you're in Indonesia when you're in these countries where you can accomplish things a lot more quickly
It's almost like your time is more valuable. It's this weird thing
somebody in Indonesia because things are cheaper because time costs less you
could literally accomplish more she is wasting her time this person is in
Indonesia she could be helping her country she could be fixing shit for
her town and instead she's wasting her effort not oh I'm going to
I'm gonna talk about drama. I'm gonna talk about this bullshit. I'm gonna talk about this
I'm gonna talk about that
You're fucking stupid. What drama am I talking about? Let me ask you where am I talking about anybody besides you bitch?
stupid ass bitch you could be doing things there are initiatives for you to
help your community and then when I say this it's racist it's racist for me to
say you me there are community initiatives that you could be spending
your precious time on instead of joining this dream and saying oh I'm gonna join
the stream with these Americans
Keep drinking, Bodo.
You're fucking stupid.
Keep drinking.
All right. Well, what are you going to do for your community?
What are you going to do for your community?
Like I said before, I have participated in community initiatives.
I know people that are linked with community initiatives
and have created the organizations of community initiatives.
What are you doing?
I live in America.
what are you doing for your community you live in Indonesia it's a shithole it's a shithole
your country is a country that everyone is running to the west to come from you understand that
and you're over here wasting your time talking to americans oh i'm gonna talk about drama
and you're trying to talk shit about me you stupid fucking idiot
where are you making your way to Europe where are you making your way to
America are you dumb are you dumb I'm already here fucking stupid
I honestly I say this hoping that you make your way to better. I say this hoping that you make your way
To a better country to somewhere where you can help your family and your community
You do not stay there to help your community. I said the same to Alex earlier. That's not how it works
Hello, you don't even know anything you're fucking three thousands miles away
You're gonna tell me about Mexican America. You don't even you couldn't point it to me on a map
You couldn't point it to me on a map bitch
Are you stupid in the US? I know you're fucking stupid. That was a rhetorical question
That was a rhetorical question. I don't need you to answer it. You fucking idiot
you're just fucking stupid you are just stupid you could help people that are
homeless you're here wasting your time doing this shit stupid stupid ass bitch
that's what you're doing it's hilarious it's hilarious how do I know when this
is charged no cool look at the manual
Okay, I mean if you plug it in the computer will tell you there's like software
I came to talk with with mr. Sike even someone man show some teddy
Hurry up main channel disappear, and I'm trying asking what happened and then you
Keep drinking
We drinking
Make your brain here's my neck
Here's how I'm gonna finish one in this talk
I'm just let me finish while in this fucking
Shit I'm swallowing you means statement that she just said
She's taking a key drink is all if I die on stream is her fault
W and I'm a sue. I'm a sue her and take her family's what hood
W I'ma take the what hood that her family works from
W
No signal you don't I'm telling you get the fuck out of there. What do you think Mexicans did bitch?
What do you think Mexicans did?
Get out of there make more fucking money get out of there. What the fuck stupid ass
tripping
I'm being discriminatory because I'm telling you to make more money
Stupid ass bitch
I'm I'm weeping. You could see the tears out of my face. You're crying a lot. You're crying a lot
I'm not even screaming at you. I'm crying
Poor you. I feel so pity about stupid ass bitch. I
Feel bad that you're in Indonesia
You live in a shithole
That's what I feel bad about
I'm trying to help you. I'm trying to get you out of that shit. You know what it is you mean
I'm trying to say shit to you so that you get out of that shithole
Make money and then come back to your shithole and make it not a shithole. You know what I mean?
Yeah, you know how Mexicans do it. They leave the rancho. That's what it is nigga. That's what I'm saying
You you grow up in the ranch or you come out of the ranch or and you fucking come back
with money
What you gotta be more specific?
You gotta be more specific or I know you'll pick any fat man you can get but you got to be more specific
What kind of job that you do for living?
I
Make like a hundred times more money than you do. I'm gonna tell you that right now
My job my career makes 100 times
Like 203, I'm not gonna give you any proof the fuck I'm why do I need to prove it to you bitch?
I'm living my life. I need to prove nothing to you. What the fuck
Signal the real one have the proof the real one have the validation
but not yes I don't need any proof for validation bitch you're stupid you're
scared huh you cannot even I'm terrified stupid bitch
no thing about you you don't even yeah it's like no why are you still here you
should do whatever don't give a fuck you stupid
bitch that's why I'm still here that's why
I will fuck Alexandra mayors in her pussy with no condom. I don't give a fuck
This is I would do that. I didn't say that for you bitch. I don't need that. I didn't say that for you bitch
Stupid ass. You didn't hear me. Are you dick? Your dick is so lonely. I knew it
I need to move your cat, baby, because I want to connect my...
You're so lonely. You never be so much of a woman, I think.
You sound really funny.
I think that, yeah.
You're funny.
You sound really funny.
Y'all already said Alexander Mayer. Oh, there's a monkey
Alexander Mayer's, Alexander Mayer's comes in New York. I'm a
fuck that. I'm a fucker. You can hang out. You can hang out
with the woman from Mexico having a monkey face. Okay,
there's God. Oh my God. What happened? What happened?
I'm asking you what happened when ghosts have to stingers, what happens they know what happened, why, what happened bitch?
Yo, what happened to my boyfriend? Where'd my boyfriend go?
Hey, faggot, we're talking real quick.
Where'd the ghosts come from?
Shut up bitch, shut up bitch, don't you ever talk to me like that, bitch.
Yeah
Who are you?
Sable ghost takes up in ghost coming here
I mean
Hello, you mean
Hello, mr. Ghost. Mr. Ghost. I need to know I someone mentioned
From the dark room that mr. Sike
Main channel disappeared what happened
Yeah, he had to make it. Well, you know that. Yeah, it just appeared, but it's another channel.
We're on here now, Don Clarkson.
Yeah, I feel I feel I feel sorry about what happened. I mean I came here because someone mentioned
What missus psyche have a new account what happened with his main account? I mean yeah, cool
What's your point? What's your point?
Yeah, it's not easy build the channel his channel with the like a 2k 2 point
to .6k subscribers I mean I hope I hope Mr. Psyche can can bring back all the subscribers now I mean
yeah I feel I feel I mean yeah I don't know thank you thank you for your point of view I don't
nobody gives a fuck
know I know some people try to you know what I I I I met some you know like I
can say these trolls try to you know like it's taking down I'll take it down
someone's channel just because they cannot have more subscribers even like a
What are you talking about?
I'm asking this aside, child.
Let me explain it to you real quick.
You're on this new channel, Dumpfrog.
Obviously, you're showing us some love, Dumpfrog.
You're a part of the... you're here.
What's your argument?
Shut the fuck up.
I just came... I just came...
My boy asked to start a new channel, yeah.
I just came today.
You're here.
Are you not here?
I'm here.
Now exactly suspect the fuck up not for the last week. I
Don't know what happened saying
That's the day of my channel. So if you're here last week, but not this week
You're lying your ass off because
Psychic main channel not about you asshole. Yeah, it's a new channel. Don't fuck. I'm not talking about me dumb dumb
You're dumb
How am I dumb explain?
How am I dumb? Good.
Um, Mrs. Seikir, it's better than asking you than this troll around.
Good. How am I dumb? How am I dumb? No! How am I dumb? Good.
You were dumb.
Look at you. You're gonna set the you're gonna set there and set the fuck up on you
Yeah, okay, cool. You sound like an old man. No, you're gonna set there and shut the fuck up guess
Yeah uncle goes not mr. Goes tell me daddy goes tell me daddy goes. No, thank you. No, thank you
Oh, I'm sorry daddy. So you have fed a file. I'm yet. Tell me a service
Mr. Psyche I came I asked miss
Yeah, I'm asking miss Alice Alexa what happened with your man
And now you came back and I hope you can reach
Good to have nothing. I'll play
I'm gonna just return that shit
again and
Just be careful. Just be careful for some trolls cyber trolls try to take it. You know what, you know
You know the biggest one is it seems
It seems it goes he's the biggest troll ever
One psyche about guns. He's the biggest drawer of her ghost is a piece of shit. He likes to use a big troll
Want him you don't know the meaning of troll uncle uncle goes
Daddy goes daddy
The Trolls the cyber trolls never gone cam
To harassing people the real people and
Oh
You're also fucking retarded. You're also not innocent. You also don't know what the fuck you're talking about. You also don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
You also don't know what the fuck you're talking about. But now listen ma'am. Listen ma'am. I'm big as a talk. I'm talking. Shut up.
Listen, you shouldn't... you shouldn't... I would be respectful.
Even the rooster looks like you, uncle.
Oh God. The rooster?
Yeah, old man.
Nope.
Can you growing up? How? How? How? Can you grow up? I can't grow up. Can you, uh?
No, I can't grow up. The rooster is coming. You ate me, so go ahead. You can have it. Mr.
Psyche, just be careful with the side patrol who tried. Mr. Psyche, be careful of ghosts.
I agree with you, Mr. Psyche. Be careful of ghosts. Be good. Just be careful of that. I agree.
Make sure you have a more if you have us if you have a small circle with the quality people not quantity
Yeah, dumbass you realize like the past month and then like I guess over
the past month
Someone with the quality
Have to join back outside
Uncle goes you don't have a quality. I'm sure that you don't have a value to okay girls. Can you
What's that?
I can see you won that one.
I'm not sure. I'm not. I just came today.
Okay, cool. Sorry, can you join back up?
So I came today and I saw signals about the drama.
Alright, can you join back up?
And now you.
I'm sorry, uncle goes. What do you want? I'm sorry, Mr. Psyche
Indonesia
Oh, I will sing for you, Mr. Psyche, I hope you're doing well and I hope you can I hope you can you know
You can't build your new channel without
stupid side patrols try to
Take it down your main channel again like a like a like a something
Yeah, and for the modes and the for the modes from the from the side channel I
Feel so pity about all of you
The way I the way I am attacking back when you guys make fun with my gender
When I am totally old woman. I'm not even stand for the transgender person
And you guys keep calling me as a man. You guys keep
Trauma as a man when I always go on cam when I talk like this. I'm using my real voice
Not even voice maker or something like that
Come on, come on up here face me. I'm not I'm not I'm not on mr. Psyche
I'm not on mr. Psyche stream like a 24-7 not even like every day. No, it's not
Uncle ghost
Is she dead?
What happened
What happened? What happened? What happened?
Dana, I'm good enough all the way back.
Granny, Granny Jamie, your energy, your energy is a, is a bad, bad energy because of you.
I'm sure Mr. Saipir lost his medical.
Oh, Mr. Sensory, if you're still crying, this is gonna start calling people monkey. Yeah.
Yeah, Rain, you have a monkey face. You never go on camera, Rain. You're just immigrant from Mexico.
I met a good Mexican, but not for you, Rain. You're laughing about people's looks. When
Some people have seen you by accident rain. That's why you never go on camp
You you need validation to be to be a real one, but sadly you're a fake one not even real
Come up here monkey rain monkey face rain
See FF circus friends forever. Just be careful with these people Mr. Psyche. I
Always wanting oh, I always wanted
This is
Mr. Psyche are you mad at me Mr. Psyche I will I will I will try to talk with
Ms. Alexa I mean the stupid signal so racist he effect he effect Ms. Alexa
So you will end stream, you already have 400 subscribers, keep it up, I mean, you will
reach more than 2k subscribers soon.
Keep doing it, keep it up, keep it up, keep it up!
Mr. Sensitive. Crying. Crying.
I really, I, I, I, I don't know what happened with the, yesterday I'm asking Ms. Alexa about what happened with Mr. Psyche Medi-Calm with the 2K subscribers.
And then today I met her.
Miss Alexa, you're the best. Do not listen. Do not listen to what trolls, especially cyber trolls
talking about you because I've been through that. I've been a lot of things and
mostly of them never go on camp. Yeah, that's the cyber trolls, cyber trolls, cyber trolls.
What happened to the viewers?
Granny Jamie
Hey, granny Jamie
You you you really know what happened with mr. Stikey
and you
What is it term time?
Same team big team
You guys really know what happened with the missus psyche man account
right
YouTube remove his man account because all of you all of us cyber trolls, right?
You guys not you guys have you guys nothing to do
Where the echoes fall